vfiles.com 2014-03-26

# VFILES

If you have any questions about your order, please email [shop@vfiles.com](mailto:shop@vfiles.com) or call 212.804.6400 x 720 Monday-Saturday 11AM-6PM EST. 

For all other inquiries, please contact us here. 

Merchandise in saleable condition with all original tags attached may be returned or exchanged within 14 days of receiving your shipment. Merchandise must be in its original packaging with all tags attached and accompanied by both the original sales receipt and a return authorization number. 

To receive a return authorization number: 

Email shop@vfiles.com and provide your name, order number, name of item(s) you wish to return, and reason for return. 

VFILES is not responsible for return shipping costs. We reserve the right to deny a refund if the returned merchandise does not meet our return policy requirements. 

All sales final on markdowns, international orders, phone and special orders, pre-orders, socks, swimwear, jewelry, eyewear, fragrances, CDs, books, stationery, magazines, toys, and specific brand and specialty items. 

We do not offer price adjustments. 

Shipping costs are non-refundable, and international customers are responsible for any duties/taxes that may apply. 

In-store return policy 

Unworn merchandise can be exchanged for merchandise or store credit within 14 days with a receipt present. Socks, swimwear, jewelry, eyewear, fragrances, CDs, books, stationery, magazines, toys, and discounted merchandise are final sale and can not be returned or exchanged. 

Returns Policy Requirements 

We reserve the right to refuse a return if the merchandise in question does not meet our standards. All merchandise must be in saleable condition when returned to VFILES. 

Where provided, all original packaging to accompany the item—including belts, shoe boxes, eyewear cases, authenticity cards, and dust bags—must be included and returned in its original condition. 

Shoes that are returned with marked soles, without a box, or in a damaged box may not be accepted, and may be sent back to the customer. 

Customers are responsible for paying for shipping, and purchasing tracking/delivery confirmation. In the event that a customer foregoes secured tracking, VFILES is not responsible for the package if it is lost or otherwise not received. 

PLEASE NOTE: We do not offer returns or exchanges for phone orders, special orders, pre-orders, or international orders. 

Unauthorized Returns 

Any merchandise returned to VFILES without a return authorization number will incur a non-negotiable re-stocking fee at 30% of the cost of the merchandise ordered, excluding tax and shipping. 

To request a return authorization number, e-mail shop@vfiles.com and provide your name, order number, name of item(s) you wish to return, and reason for return. 

Exchanges 

All exchanges are final, and cannot be returned or exchanged further. 

All orders are processed on business days within 24 hours. 

Orders placed after 3PM EST, on weekends, or on holidays are processed the following business day. 

Please note this may take longer during sale periods or exclusive releases when it may take up to 48 hours for orders to be shipped. 

Shipping rates are determined by weight and destination at point of purchase. The origin of all VFILES orders are shipped from New York via FedEx or UPS. 

How do I track my package online? 

Upon shipment, you will receive a confirmation e-mail with your tracking number. 

You can also track your order by logging into your account and seeing your order history. 

Once your order has shipped from our store, please directly contact your courier with any inquiries about the status of your package. FedEx can be reached by calling 1-800-463-3339 or online at fedex.com. UPS can be reached by calling 1-800-742-5877 or online at ups.com. 

International Orders 

All international orders require a signature for delivery. 

Some international orders over $1000 are subject to being held at the nearest FedEx or UPS location for pick-up where signature and valid ID will be required. 

Customer is responsible for all customs fees unless they are explicitly charged during checkout. 

Service Delays 

VFILES is not responsible for unexpected shipping delays caused by circumstances such as severe weather or natural disasters. Similarly, we are not responsible for unexpected shipping delays caused by circumstances related to the courier itself, such as clearance delays. In cases such as these, please contact your courier with any inquiries about the status of your package. 

If you have any questions about your order, please email shop@vfiles.com or call 212.804.6400 x 720 Monday-Saturday 11AM-6PM EST. 

Failed Deliveries & Returned Packages 

In the case that the courier is unable to deliver a package due to an incorrect address entered by the customer, the customer’s refusal to pay duties, multiple failed attempts to reach the customer at point of delivery or otherwise, VFILES is not responsible for payment of return shipping costs levied by the courier. Similarly, VFILES is not responsible for the payment of re-shipping merchandise to the customer. In cases such as these, the customer is responsible for all shipping costs associated with returned packages due to failed delivery. 

Welcome to VFILES! VFILES is a fashion entertainment platform. It's the past present and future of fashion - a social application and collaborative database of fashion media.....for people who love fashion and pop culture. VFiles allows you to peruse our database of content, upload your own related content, and express your own personal taste and style to your friends. You can also shop and enjoy our original programing. 

In order to use VFiles.com, we need you to agree to the following Terms of Use ("Terms"), which govern the relationship between VFiles.com, its parent company (VFILES, LLC, together with VFiles.com, "VFILES" or "We"), and users of the VFiles.com website (the "Site"). By using the Site, you agree to these Terms. Please keep in mind that we may change these Terms periodically, so you should check these documents from time to time for changes. 

1\. Creating an Account 

you will not create an account for anyone but yourself (or someone who has explicitly asked you to create an account); 

you will not provide any false personal information; 

you will not use the Site if you are under the age of 13; 

you will keep all of the information on your profile, including your contact information, up-to-date; and 

you will not share your password with other people, or allow other people to access the Site through your account. 

If we learn that you have violated this provision in any way, we reserve the right to terminate your account immediately. 

We allow you to create and access your account by using other social networking sites, such as Facebook and Twitter. If you connect to VFiles through sites like these, you give us permission to access and use your information from these sites as permitted by those sites. Please take a look at our Privacy Policy for additional information. 

2\. Uploading and Sharing Information 

Once you create an account, you will be able to post content to the Site, including photos, comments, messages to other users, etc. ("Content"). When you upload Content, you represent that you created the Content, or that the owner of the Content has granted you the right to upload the Content to the Site. 

You will retain ownership in anything that you upload to the Site. However, you also agree to grant us a non-exclusive, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use any Content that you post on the Site. This license ends when you delete the Content from your profile or from the Site, unless the Content has also been posted on other users’ profiles and has not been deleted from those profiles. Once Content is deleted from your profile, neither you nor other users will have access to it. 

When you share Content on your profile, it may be available to other users (depending on the privacy settings for your profile). We cannot control what these users do with your Content outside of the Site. You should therefore think carefully about the Content that you choose to upload to the Site. Please see our Privacy Policy for more information. 

Although you may upload Content at any time upon the creation of an account, VFiles is under no obligation to continue to display uploaded Content onto the Site, and may edit, modify or remove any Content posted on the Site for any reason and at any time. 

3\. VFiles Content 

Except for the Content uploaded to the Site by you or other users described above, all text, designs, photographs, photo layouts, audio and video content, and editorial content, and other multimedia content on the Site (together, “VFiles Content”) are the property of VFiles and its licensors. You agree that you will not modify, reproduce, distribute, sell, license, or otherwise exploit the VFiles Content without our permission. 

Once you create an account, we grant you a limited, non-exclusive license to access and view the VFiles Content for your own personal, non-commercial use within the Site. Please keep in mind that we can terminate this license at any time for any reason or no reason, and that we are free to remove any VFiles Content from the Site at any moment, without any advance notice to you. 

4\. Prohibited Activities 

Our primary objective is to create a tolerant and safe online community for people interested in fashion and pop culture to access content from a wide range of publications, comment upon and share such content with other users, and use such content and comments to create a user profile that showcases his or her distinctive style to the world. In order to make this happen, you agree that you will not compromise or jeopardize other users’ experiences by:\ 

using the Site to transmit unapproved or unsolicited commercial messages; 

using an automated process to access the Site for the purposes of gathering the private information of other users; or 

You further agree that you will not - 

uploading any kind of malicious code to the Site. 

ask for or utilize any other user’s account information; 

post the private information of another user; 

post Content that harasses, threatens, or abuses any person or entity by any means, including the use of vulgar, hateful, racially or ethnically offensive, sexually harassing, or otherwise objectionable Content; 

upload any libelous or defamatory Content about other users; 

upload any obscene or pornographic Content; 

upload any Content that is offensively violent; or 

impersonate any other person, including other users or VFiles administrators. 

If you believe that another user’s conduct violates these standards, you agree that you will report such conduct or Content to us by sending an e-mail to abuse@vfiles.com. While we reserve the right to take down any content that violates these standards, we do not assume a duty or responsibility to do so. 

5\. Protecting Third Party Rights 

We reserve the right to 

take down any profile that we believe is false or contains false information; 

take down any Content that we believe infringes upon the intellectual property rights of a third party, including but not limited to copyright, trademark, patent, trade secrets, rights of publicity, or any other intellectual property right; or 

take down any Content that we believe otherwise violates these Terms. 

We do not assume a duty or responsibility to review Content to ensure that it does not violate the standards of this section. That said, we have a policy through which third parties can ask us to take down Content that infringes upon their intellectual property rights, which appears in Section 6 (below). When we receive take down requests, we will try to address or resolve the request or complaint within 72 hours. 

6\. Procedure for Reporting Infringing and False Content 

Any requests to take down Content that is false or that infringes upon your intellectual property rights should be sent to abuse@vfiles.com. Any such complaints or requests should include your name, your mailing address, your telephone number and your e-mail address. 

Copyright Infringement 

If you send us a request to take down Content that infringes upon your copyright, your request should include (a) a description of the Content you believe infringes upon your copyright; (b) the name of the copyrighted work you believe is being infringed, (c) the Site URL that contains the infringing Content, and (d) a short explanation of how the Content infringes your rights. Please note that we have designated the following agent for such copyright complaints or requests under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”):\ 

Copyright complaints and requests can be sent directly to:\ 

VFILES Copyright Agent 

12 Mercer Street 

New York, NY 10013 

abuse@vfiles.com 

212-804-6400 

Other Intellectual Property Infringement 

If you send us a request to take down Content that infringes upon any other intellectual property rights (e.g. trademarks, patents, trade secrets, rights of publicity, etc.), your complaint or request should include (a) the intellectual property you own that is being infringed; (b) a description of the Content you believe infringes upon your intellectual property; (c) the Site URL that contains the infringing Content, and (d) a short explanation of how the Content infringes your rights. 

Fake Profiles 

If someone has created a profile in which he or she pretends to be you, and you send us a request to take down that profile, please be sure that you have included the URL of your profile and the fake profile, and that you clearly indicate which profile is the fake profile. 

Next Steps 

Once we receive a complaint, we will make best efforts to review the complaint as soon as possible. If you have provided us all of the information above, we will promptly remove or block access to the Content or the fake profile, and will send a notice to the other VFiles user indicating that we have done so. We will terminate the accounts of any repeat infringers at our discretion. 

Counter Notice 

If we send you a notice that we’ve removed your Content from the Site because it is fake or because it infringes upon another party’s intellectual property rights, and you believe that we acted as a result of misidentification or error, you can lodge a Counter Notice by e-mailing us at abuse@vfiles.com. Any Counter Notice should include (a) your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address, (b) an identification of the material that we took down, (c) a statement that you have a good faith belief that the material was removed as a result of mistake or misidentification, (d) a statement that you consent to the jurisdiction of the U.S. District Court for the federal district in which you reside, and that you will accept service of process from the complaining party or its agent in the event that a law suit is filed against you relating to such Content, and (e) your physical or electronic signature. 

If we receive such a Counter Notice, we will put the removed Content back on your profile, unless we first receive notice from the complaining party that it has filed a law suit or other action seeking a court order to keep you from engaging in the allegedly infringing activity. 

7\. Conflicts Among Users 

In the event that you and another Site user have a conflict based on either of your conduct or uploaded Content, we reserve the right to take any appropriate measures to resolve the conflict, including but in no way limited to taking down any Content that violates these Terms of Use (pursuant to Section 6, above) or terminating your account (pursuant to Section 8, below). We do not, however, assume a duty or responsibility to intervene in such conflicts. 

8\. Termination 

If your use of the Site violates these Terms, indicates to us a desire to violate the spirit of these Terms, or subjects VFILES to potential legal liability, we may stop providing any or all of our services to you. This could result in a deletion of your account and any and all Content uploaded to your profile. 

You may delete your profile or account at any time. 

9\. Disclaimer 

YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS SOLELY AT YOUR OWN RISK. YOU AGREE THAT THE SITE IS PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS,” “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. WE DO NOT GUARANTEE THAT THE SITE WILL BE SAFE OR SECURE. WHILE WE WILL MAKE EVERY ATTEMPT TO KEEP THE SITE FREE FROM BUGS AND ERRORS, WE CANNOT AND DO NOT GUARANTEE CONTINUOUS, UNINTERRUPTED OR SECURE ACCESS TO THE SITE OR ITS SERVICES. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL WE BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY OTHER PARTY FOR INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES (EVEN IF SUCH DAMAGES ARE FORESEEABLE OR WHERE VFILES HAS BEEN ADVISED OR HAS KNOWLEDGE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES) ARISING FROM YOUR USE OF THE SITE. 

Idemnification

You agree to defend, release, and hold harmless VFiles and its officers, directors, employees, agents, assigns and licensors from any and all claims, demands, liability, judgments, costs and expenses (including reasonable attorney’s fees and costs) arising out of or related to any breach of these Terms. You further acknowledge that we cannot and are not responsible for any actions of third party users of the Site, or any Content, information or data posted to the Site by its users, and you hereby agree to defend, release and hold harmless VFiles and its officers, directors, employees, agents, assigns and licensors from any and all liability VFiles may have with respect to such third party actions. 

11\. Miscellaneous 

These Terms, together with the Privacy Policy, are the entire agreement between us and any users and people accessing the Site. 

If any portion of these Terms is found to be unenforceable, the remaining portion of these Terms will not be affected, and will remain in full force. 

Any failure on our part to enforce a particular term of these Terms will not constitute a waiver of that term. 

These Terms are governed by and shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the state of New York, U.S.A., without regard to its conflicts of law provisions. 

This Privacy Policy is designed to inform you of the various types of information that we collect from you when you use the VFiles.com web site (the “Site”). By using the Site, you acknowledge and agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating the information posted to the website. We’ll let you know when we make changes to our Privacy Policy by posting a “last modified” date at the top of this page. However, since any amendments that we make will become effective as soon as we post them, you should periodically visit this page to review our current Privacy Policy, so that you are aware of any revisions. If you have any concerns, questions or disputes related to our Privacy Policy, please direct them to support@vfiles.com. 

The Information We Collect and How We Use It 

When you visit the Site, you provide us with two types of information:/ personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. 

Personally Identifiable Information 

If you create a user profile with us, we’ll ask you to provide basic information about yourself that could be used to identify you, such as your name, your e-mail address, your telephone number, your address, and/or a photograph of yourself (together, “Profile Information”). We also collect and store information you place on your user profile (e.g. information about your favorite designers, your personal style) and information contained in messages you send to other VFiles.com users. If you connect to VFiles.com through a third-party social networking website like Facebook or Twitter, we may also use personal information from those profiles. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to all of the above information as “Personal Information.” 

With respect to Profile Information, we will display Profile Information to other VFiles.com users in order to allow you to connect with other VFiles.com users. Of course, you can choose your own privacy settings, which can restrict the amount of Profile Information that can be seen or accessed by other VFiles.com users. If you have any questions about how to change your privacy settings, drop us a note at support@vfiles.com. 

We use Personal Information to customize your experience within the Site. For example, we use Personal Information to provide you with recommendations for specific Content available on the Site, to allow you to easily return to posts and messages made by you or other Site users, and to return to searches that you’ve conducted within the Site. We will never intentionally share your personally identifiable information with any third party without first obtaining your permission to do so. 

On occasion, we may also use your Personal Information to contact you with our newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, or other information that we think would be of interest to you. You can tell us to stop sending these kinds of communications to you at any time, either by updating your “preferences” information in your account settings, or by following the “unsubscribe” instructions provided in any of the communications we send you. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

When you enter the Site, we automatically collect information about your browser type and your Internet Protocol (IP) address(es), as well as information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (for example, websites you might have visited before you visited the Site, the amount of time you spend on those sites). We also collect information that you provide to us when you sign up to use the Site that cannot reasonably be used to identify or contact you – such information includes information about the various demographic groups you fall into (e.g. age group, income group, etc.), as well as information relating to your use of the Site (e.g. the types of Content you search for on the Site, the times of day you access the Site, etc.). In this Privacy Policy, we refer to all of the above as “Non-Personally Identifiable Information.” 

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information in the aggregate to monitor the web site, to improve the web site’s offerings, to customize your experience with the Site, and for targeted advertising. Advertising is conducted by third parties, who will have access to your IP address when their ads are displayed on the page you are viewing. These third parties have no access to your personally identifiable information unless you’ve chosen to share it with them. 

Privacy Policy Cookies

We use “cookies,” which are small text files that are stored on your computer that retain your information and preferences relative to your activities on the website. They are meant to enhance your experience on the Site, and are used primarily to recognize registered users who are logged on. For example, if you tell us to, we will send a cookie to your machine that remembers your login credentials to the Site, so you don’t have to enter them every time you access the Site. 

Should you wish to prevent your computer from accepting cookies from the Site, you can change the settings on your web browser to either block cookies sent from the web site, or to disable cookies altogether. Please note that the Site may not function properly, or may function differently, if you choose not to receive cookies. 

Other Permitted Uses of Your Information 

We have the right to provide your information to third parties such as web hosting companies to the extent it is necessary to keep the Site up and operating. We have the right to disclose and transfer user lists and related personally identifiable information in connection with any merger, sale or contemplated sale of all or part of our business related to the web site, and to treat such information as a business asset in the event of bankruptcy or liquidation. We may also disclose personally identifiable information to a third party if disclosure is required to comply with a subpoena, court order, and/or other legal instrument, legal proceeding or relevant law, or if there is an immediate, imminent threat to the safety of any person, VFiles or the Site. 

Editing Information 

You may edit or delete any information provided to us at any time by editing your user profile. To delete your account entirely, please e-mail contact@vfiles.com. 

Privacy 

In order to protect your information, we use industry-standard security methods such as firewalls, encryption security layers and secured socket layers. We also permit you to create your own privacy settings, in order to control the specific information that is available to other users of the Site. However, no security measures are perfect, and we therefore cannot guarantee that the steps we have taken to secure your information will prevent our systems from being compromised and/or your information from being disclosed. 

With respect to information you choose to share on the Site, you essentially control your own destiny. You can change the Privacy Settings for your profile so that certain information that you share is not accessible by the general public or by other users. However, keep in mind that the Privacy Settings cannot be used to keep everything private – by way of example, if you comment upon VFiles Content (as defined in the Terms of Use), those comments will be accessible to any registered user of the Site. Moreover, even if you delete content that you post on the Site, other users may have already downloaded or otherwise kept that content, and the content could potentially be accessible through archived pages of the Site. It’s very important that you think carefully before you post any private information to the Site. If you have any questions about how to keep your information private on the Site, please e-mail us at support@vfiles.com, and we’ll do our best to help. 

Links 

We may contain links to websites that are not affiliated with VFiles, and whose data security and privacy policies may differ from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy policies employed by third party sites. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any site that is accessed from the site so that you will be aware of how each visited site collects, uses and distributes information. 

Children Under the Age of 13 

VFiles.com is designed solely for users over the age of 13. We do not knowingly solicit or collect any information about users who may be under the age of 13, and will delete any information provided by such individuals as soon as possible. Please do not provide us with any personal information if you are under the age of 13. 

We do allow users between the ages of 13 and 18 to use the site. However, such users should discuss the use of VFiles.com or any other social networking site with their parents before they submit, share or post any content to the Site.
